ILGWU. Carl Proper papers 5780/150
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- United Mine Workers: Enoxy Demonstration, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  Letter from Trumka to Mazur asking for support for picketing the U.S. corporate headquarters of Enoxy Coal Corporation's parent company, Ente Nazionale Indocarbusi (ENI), in NY; UMW press releases, press statement at demonstration, newspaper clippings; letter from U.S. Dept. of State to Italian Ministry of Budget re alleged violations of guidelines for multinational enterprises
- Energy Cost Issues, 1987-1989 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Sub-metering, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- New York City Business Services, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Jay Mazur, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Correspondence, 1991-1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Clinton Trade Policy: NAFTA/NAO, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- New York City Planning Study, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- New York City Department of City Planning, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- New York City Planning: Schaffer, 1990-1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Chinatown Zoning Study, 1991-1992 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Brooklyn Planning, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Mankoff Response to Citywide Industry Study, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- New York City Productivity Council, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- New York City: Tax Breaks, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- New York City Workforce Development Commission (WDC), 1994 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- New York City Workforce Development Commission (WDC): Final Report, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- New York City: Mayor Giuliani Communications, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- New York City: Giuliani Administration, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association (AACA) (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Council for American Fashion (CAF): Tax Exemption, 1992-1994 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Council for American Fashion (CAF): Meeting, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Council for American Fashion (CAF): Forms, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Pennsylvania Labor-Management: Application for Exemption, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Council for American Fashion (CAF): Insurance, 1992-1993 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Council for American Fashion (CAF): Shimmy Cohen Contract, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Council for American Fashion (CAF): Shimmy Cohen, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Eastern Region Apparel Labor-Management Council: Conference, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Arnold Delin (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association (AACA): Riverview, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- Eastern Pennsylvania and New Jersey Council for American Fashion (CAF), 1994 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  March
- Lehigh Valley Exit Survey, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- Lehigh Valley Exit Survey, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Lehigh Valley Exit Survey: Year 3, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Eastern Region Apparel Labor-Management Council: Bylaws (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Eastern Region Apparel Labor-Management Council: Meeting, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  July 1
- Eastern Pennsylvania Council for American Fashion (CAF): Funds, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Council for American Fashion (CAF): Memo, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Council for American Fashion (CAF): Listing, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Eastern Region Apparel Labor-Management Council: Articles, Bylaws, and Amendments, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Eastern Region Apparel Labor-Management Council: Meeting, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  May 5
- Eastern Region Apparel Labor-Management Council: Projects, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Mid-Atlantic Regional Employee Involvement Council, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Eastern Region Apparel Labor-Management Council: MRC, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Eastern Region Apparel Labor-Management Council: Meetings, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  February 1
- Kahn, Karpman, Proper, and Delin Correspondence, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- The Limited: Pennsylvania, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Eastern Region Apparel Labor-Management Council: Meeting, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  September 1
- Eastern Region Apparel Labor-Management Council: Meeting, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  November 9
- Greater Blouse, 1993-1995 (Box 26, Folder 31)
- Exports, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 32)
- Greater Blouse: Strategic Program, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 33)
- Greater Blouse, 1993-1994 (Box 26, Folder 34)
- Greater Blouse: Labor-Management Committee, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 35)
- Supervisory and Shopleader Training, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 36)
- Exodus from Apparel, 1990 (Box 26, Folder 37)
- New York is Fashion, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 38)
  2 copies
- Eastern Region Apparel Labor-Management Council: Letterhead (Box 26, Folder 39)
- Greater Blouse: Asian Media, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 40)
- Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association (AACA): Show, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 41)
- Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association (AACA): Online Database Correspondence, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 42)
- Before 1990 (Box 26, Folder 43)
- Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association (AACA) and Garment Industry Development Corporation (GDIC) Homepages, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 44)
- Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association (AACA), 1989-1996 (Box 26, Folder 45)
- Roosevelt Reelection Scrapbook, 1936 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Minutes, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  September 28-29
- General Executive Board (GEB): Regional Reports, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  September
- General Executive Board (GEB): Department Reports, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Reports, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Read on Cards, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- ILGWU Policy Statements, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  June
- ILGWU Stationary (Box 28, Folder 7)
- David Melman Stationary (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Trip Planning, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Irwin Solomon Report, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Committees List, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Minutes, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Regional Reports, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Department Reports, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Reports, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Minutes, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  February
- General Executive Board (GEB): Regional Reports [folder 1 of 2], 1994 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Regional Reports [folder 2 of 2], 1994 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Department Reports, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Reports, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Executive Committee Minutes, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  December 8
- General Executive Board (GEB): Executive Committee Minutes, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  March 8
- General Executive Board (GEB): Minutes, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  October
- General Executive Board (GEB): Reports, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Minutes, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Regional Reports, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Executive Session, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Financial Statement, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Census and Finances, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Topics, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Executive Committee, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  February 5
- General Executive Board (GEB): Jay Mazur Announcements, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 32)
- General Executive Board (GEB): Finances, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 33)
- General Executive Board (GEB): UNITE Ad Campaign, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 34)
- Jay Mazur Read at Board Meeting, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 35)
- Fashion Exports New York: Database, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Fashion Exports New York: Export Correspondence, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Fashion Exports New York: Leah Kaplan, 1993-1995 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Fashion Exports New York: Governor's Award, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Fashion Exports New York: Media, 1994-1995 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Fashion Exports New York: Manager Messages, 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Exports: Vigdor Workshop, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Fashion Exports New York: Publications, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Fashion Exports New York: Company Profiles (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Fashion Exports New York: International Business Seminar, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Council for American Fashion: Apparel Contractors Seminar, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- Council for American Fashion: European Market Entry, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC): Keeping New York in Fashion, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- AFL-CIO Industrial Union Department: Technology and Work Organization Seminar, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- National Conference on Women Garment Workers, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Safer Workplace Seminar, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- New York is Fashion, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT): Japan Apparel Initiative Seminar, 1991 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- Eastern Pennsylvania: Council for American Fashion (CAF), 1994 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Eastern Pennsylvania: Council for American Fashion (CAF) Meeting, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  January
- Eastern Pennsylvania: Council for American Fashion (CAF) Easton/Bethlehem, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  June 8
- Eastern Pennsylvania: Ardmore/Quartet Project, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Eastern Pennsylvania Labor-Management: Kaufman Meeting, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  April 20
- Eastern Pennsylvania: Atlantic Apparel Contractors Association (AACA), 1993-1994 (Box 29, Folder 24)
- Eastern Pennsylvania: Arnold Delin, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 25)
- Business Surveys, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 26)
- Council for American Fashion (CAF): Steering Committee Meeting, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  September 22
- Council for American Fashion (CAF): Steering Committee Meeting, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  September 10
- Council for American Fashion (CAF): Steering Committee Meeting, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  January 20
- Pennsylvania Contractors Seminar, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 30)
- Boston Contractors Seminar, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  January 11
- New York Contractors Seminar, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  February 10
- Council for American Fashion (CAF) Public Relations: American Fashion Designers Show, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 33)
- Public Relations, 1995 (Box 29, Folder 34)
- Public Relations Brochure, 1994 (Box 29, Folder 35)
- Council for American Fashion (CAF) Brochure, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 36)
- Council for American Fashion (CAF) Public Relations: Brochure and Mailing List, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 37)
- Council for American Fashion (CAF) Public Relations, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 38)
- Fashion Industry Promotion Group, 1990-1991 (Box 29, Folder 39)
- Stan Herman New York Times Op/Ed, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  March 28
- Seventh Avenue to City Hall, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 41)
- Seventh on Six, 1993 (Box 29, Folder 42)
- Convention and Committee Reports and Oversight Notes [folder 1 of 3], 1995 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Convention and Committee Reports and Oversight Notes [folder 2 of 3], 1995 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Convention and Committee Reports and Oversight Notes [folder 3 of 3], 1995 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  October 1992 - January 1993
- Correspondence, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  February - May
- Correspondence, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  June - September
- Triangle Fire Miscellaneous (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Triangle Fire Exhibit Layout (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Sequins, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Sequins, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- LaGuardia Community College, 1993-1997 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- IGLWU Health Service, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Sweatshop State Enforcement: New Jersey, 1994-1996 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Sweatshop State Enforcement: New York, 1992-1996 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Sweatshop Enforcement: Spitzer, 1997-1998 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Garment Industry Advisory Committee (GIAC), 1999 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Garment Industry Day Care Center of Chinatown Brochure (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Brooklyn Garment Industry Study, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Sunset Park [folder 1 of 2], 1996 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Sunset Park [folder 2 of 2], 1996 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Draft Merger Constitution [folder 1 of 3], 1995 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  February 16
- Draft Merger Constitution [folder 2 of 3], 1995 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Draft Merger Constitution [folder 3 of 3], 1995 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- New Jersey Garment Industry Advisory Committee, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 18)
- Textile/Clothing Technology Corporation (TC2), 1992-1993 (Box 31, Folder 19)
- Textile/Clothing Technology Corporation (TC2): Ergonomics, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 20)
- Textile/Clothing Technology Corporation (TC2): Brand, 1992-1994 (Box 31, Folder 21)
- Textile/Clothing Technology Corporation (TC2), 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 22)
- Textile/Clothing Technology Corporation (TC2): Interactive Distance Learning Network, 1995-1999 (Box 31, Folder 23)
- Textile/Clothing Technology Corporation (TC2), 1994-1995 (Box 31, Folder 24)
- Textile/Clothing Technology Corporation (TC2): Dues and Bills, 1992-1995 (Box 31, Folder 25)
- Textile/Clothing Technology Corporation (TC2): Quick Response, 1993 (Box 31, Folder 26)
- Textile/Clothing Technology Corporation (TC2): Board Meeting Minutes, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  March 29
- Triangle Fire, 1987-1993 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- ILGWU Miscellaneous Publications (Box 32, Folder 2)
- ILGWU Citations Cornell University, 1991 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- ILGWU Literacy Program Magazines, 1986-1991 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- George Meany Biography, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Diego Rivera: Paradise Lost, 1989 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- New York, Our City, Our Union, 1940 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Zoning and Blueprints [folder 1 of 2], 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Zoning and Blueprints [folder 2 of 2], 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- New York Industrial Retention Network (NYIRN): Garment Center Land Use Analysis [folder 1 of 3], 2001 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  April 9 copies total
- New York Industrial Retention Network (NYIRN): Garment Center Land Use Analysis [folder 2 of 3], 2001 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- New York Industrial Retention Network (NYIRN): Garment Center Land Use Analysis [folder 3 of 3], 2001 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- New York Industrial Retention Network (NYIRN): Garment Center Land Use Analysis Executive Summary, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  April 8 copies
- Garment Center Employment and Real Estate Profile, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  October 2 copies
- Committee to Preserve the Garment Center (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Albany: Sheldon Silver, Speaker of the House, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Zoning Press Conference, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  April
- White Paper Distribution, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Move Smart, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Zoning Press Conference Follow-up Letters, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Press Conference Mailings, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Schumer, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 22)
- Real Estate Issues, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 23)
- Real Estate Press Conference, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 24)
- Zoning, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 25)
- New York Industrial Retention Network (NYIRN): Breakfast, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 26)
- Zoning Meeting, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 27)
  February 6
- Zoning, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 28)
- Zoning Meeting 3, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 29)
  November 27
- Zoning Meeting, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 30)
  December 11
- Zoning Group Meeting, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 31)
  October 25
- Zoning Rules Background, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 32)
- Spitzer, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 33)
- Schumer Meeting, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 34)
- Planning Meeting 1, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 35)
  October 13
- Zoning State/City Agenda, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 36)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation (GIDC) Chinatown Meeting, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 37)
  November
- Zoning Chinatown, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 38)
- Fact Sheets, 1998-2000 (Box 32, Folder 39)
- Fashion Center New York City: Tenant Survey, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Fashion Center New York City: Economic Profile, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Fashion Center New York City: Economic Profile 1997 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Fashion Center New York City: Economic Profile, 200 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Walsam 36 Company Economic Analysis Report, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Miller Advertising Agency (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Zoning: Kurzman Karelsen and Frank (Box 33, Folder 7)
- New York City Atlas of Industrial Areas, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- New Opportunities for a Changing Economy in New York City, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Zoning: 315-325 West 36th Street, 1998 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Zoning: Chelsea (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Zoning: Real Estate Board of New York, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Schumer Communication, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- K. Fried, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Municipal Art Society, 2001 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Zoning: Community Board Memo, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  September 26
- Zoning: Media (Box 33, Folder 17)
- New York Industrial Retention Network (NYIRN) Study, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Garment Center Study, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 19)
- Factory Space Buroughs, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 20)
- New York Industrial Retention Network (NYIRN): Manhattan Report, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 21)
- Linda Dworak, Garment Industry Development Corporation: Testimony, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  September 28
- Zoning: Association Meeting (Box 33, Folder 23)
- 91 East Broadway, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 24)
- Fashion Center Business Survey, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 25)
- Pine Fashions, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 26)
- Tahari Protests, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 27)
- Chinatown Survey, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 28)
- Chinatown Contractor Responses, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 29)
- Garment Center Buildings (Box 33, Folder 30)
- Municipal Art Society, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 31)
- Zoning: UNITE Strategy, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 32)
- UNITE Shop Lists (Box 33, Folder 33)
- Zoning: Pauls Study, 1996 (Box 33, Folder 34)
- Empire Zones (Box 33, Folder 35)
- Zoning and New York City's Garment Industry by Jay Mazur, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 36)
- Impact of 42nd Street Redevelopment, 1984 (Box 33, Folder 37)
- Long Island City Industry Study, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 38)
- Garment Center Survey, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 39)
- Trucking Survey, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 40)
- Zoning Survey Responses, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 41)
- Survey Responses: Suppliers, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 42)
- Survey Responses: Contractors, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 43)
- Survey Responses: Showroom, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 44)
- Queens Country Overall Economic Development Corporation, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 45)
- Organizers Survey Midtown (Box 33, Folder 46)
- Garment Center Zoning Issues, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 47)
- Zoning Meeting, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  March 7
- Zoning: Bowles Study, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 49)
- Zoning: New York Industrial Retention Network (NYIRN), 2000 (Box 33, Folder 50)
- New York Industrial Retention Network (NYIRN)/Amalgamated Bank Proposal, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 51)
- New York Industrial Retention Network (NYIRN) Hearing, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 52)
- Apparel Textile Location, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 53)
- Business Relocation Assistance, 2000 (Box 33, Folder 54)
- Marketing Workshop, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- New Jersey Labor-Management Contractor Marketing Workshop, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Made in the USA, 1992-1995 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Media, 1991-1993 (Box 34, Folder 4)
- New Jersey Computer Marking and Grading Grant, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 5)
- New Jersey Industry Service Center, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 6)
- New Jersey Apparel Industry Survey: Summary Results, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 7)
- New Jersey Apparel Industry Survey: Original Responses, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 8)
- New Jersey Industrial Modernization Project with the National Institute of Standards and Technology, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 9)
- Bronx Economic Development, 1993-1995 (Box 34, Folder 10)
- Bronx and Fernando Ferrer, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 11)
- South Bronx (SOBRO) Overall Economic Development Corporation, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 12)
- Brooklyn Focus Group, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 13)
- Brooklyn Economic Development, 1988-1991 (Box 34, Folder 14)
- Queens Economic Development, 1988-1991 (Box 34, Folder 15)
- Pennsylvania Government Assistance (Box 34, Folder 16)
- Pennsylvania Ben Franklin Centers, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 17)
- Rand Corporation Requests, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 18)
- Garment Industry Development Corporation and Council for American Fashion Services, 1991-1994 (Box 34, Folder 19)
- Regional Planning Authority, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 20)
- Region Plan Association, 1994 (Box 34, Folder 21)
- Carl Proper, Resume (Box 34, Folder 22)
- Resumes, 1991-1995 (Box 34, Folder 23)
- Research on Apparel Networks and Channel Partnerships, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 24)
- Clemson University: Apparel Research, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 25)
- Columbia University: Palpacuer Study [folder 1 of 2], 1995 (Box 34, Folder 26)
- Columbia University: Palpacuer Study [folder 2 of 2], 1995 (Box 34, Folder 27)
- Cornell University: Apparel and Textiles, 1990-1995 (Box 34, Folder 28)
- Cornell University: New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 29)
- Cornell University: New York Conference, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  October 14
- City University of New York, 1992-1993 (Box 34, Folder 31)
- City University of New York: Industrial Relations Seminar, 1989-1990 (Box 34, Folder 32)
- City University of New York: Labor-Management Research by Menzi, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 33)
- Fashion Institute of Technology: Incubator, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 34)
- Fashion Institute of Technology: Quick Response Electronic Data Interchange, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 35)
- Fashion Institute of Technology: Courses, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 36)
- Fashion Institute of Technology: Projects, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 37)
- Fashion Institute of Technology: ILG Committee, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 38)
- Harvard University: Textile Study Summary, 1994-1995 (Box 34, Folder 39)
- Harvard University: Study of U.S. Apparel Industry, 1995-1996 (Box 34, Folder 40)
- Harvard University: Study of U.S. Apparel Industry, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 41)
- Harvard University: Survey, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 42)
- Harvard University: Seminars, 1993-1994 (Box 34, Folder 43)
- Harvard University: Reports and Correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 34, Folder 44)
- Harvard University: Quick Response, 1992-1994 (Box 34, Folder 45)
- Harvard University: Miscellaneous, 1991-1992 (Box 34, Folder 46)
- John Dunlop, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 47)
  December 6
- Dunolp, Abernathy, Weil, 1991 (Box 34, Folder 48)
  June 13
- New Jersey Institute of Technology, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 49)
- New Jersey Institute of Technology: Proposal, 1993 (Box 34, Folder 50)
- Northampton Community College, 1990-1991 (Box 34, Folder 51)
- Northampton Community College: Technology Course (Box 34, Folder 52)
- Buyer Services Program, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 1)
- New York State Childcare, 1990-1994 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Commercial Rent Arbitration, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Consortium for Worker Education, 1994-1995 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Contractor Referral Services, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Curriculum: Management and Worker Training, 1987-1989 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Employers Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Enterprise Zones: Harlem-Bronx Empowerment Zone, 1995-1997 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Safer Workplace, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Fashion Center Business Improvement District (BID), 1993-1995 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- New York is Fashion, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Fashion Show, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  July 14
- Democrat Fashion Show, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Fashion Shows, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT): Electronic Data Interchange (EDI) Committee, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Fashion Institute of Technology (FIT): Hershfield, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 16)